This beautiful young man, Ralph Yall, accidentally rang the doorbell of the wrong house in Kansas City, Missouri.
He was trying to pick up his younger siblings.
The white owner of the house shot this black child in the head.
And as he lay on the ground, he shot him again as Ralph bled out.
The shooter is free.
The police said it was an error.
No charges.
This is America.
Just for even a second that this country is not riddled with racism is to be an implicit accomplice.
Right now, Ralph is fighting for his life in a hospital while his racist, terrorist, menace to society shooter gets to sleep tonight at home.
Because in this nation, a black life lost is seen as an error not worthy of consequence.
Like This Instagram is an error.
Now, look ahead.
We've got it combined with the poor side in the story.
We've got aPlaying Normal Adler on that.
We've got this wrong.
We've got two hands.
We've got this wrong하는 one.
We've got the chance to do this right there.
And this isニelman.
Now, if you haven't tried it, we haven't seen a long affair.
We've got this wrong.
We've got this wrong point.
Now, I'd love to point out my mastermind.
We've got this wrong mark.
So, buy this daily work.
We've got the ones in the building.
We've got this to tell you about how this has changed.